Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New business records, 1924-2007 and undated, bulk 1980-1989 RL.00731
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Companies Files, 1946-2005 and undated, 72 boxes
  - Courvoisier XO
    - [JWT-USA--Courvoisier XO, 1986: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 25)
  - CRESTAR
    - Annual report, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Background information packet, 1988 (Box 25)
  - Cutex
    - Northam Warren Corporation, 1958 May-1962 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 26)
  - Daewoo
    - General files, 1982-1987 (Box 26)
    - Advertising planning (Box 26)
    - Presentation book, 1982 (Box 26)
    - Results of 3-audience opinion leader survey, 1982 (Box 26)
  - Daily News
    - Background information, 1986-1987 (Box 26)
    - Information booklet, undated (Box 26)
    - Presentation, 1980, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - David T. Snyder (consultant)
    - Credentials response, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Dean Witter
    - General files, 1963 Apr.-1964 Nov. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 26)
    - Change presentation, 1989 (Box 26)
    - Credentials presentation, 1985 June 21 (Box 26)
    - Financial services background information, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Preliminary situation analysis, 1981 (Box 26)
  - Delta (faucets)
    - Project Delta--Taking On Establishment, 1989 (Box 26)
    - We Add Value presentation, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Diamond Crystal Salt
    - Acceptance of DCS in NY Spanish Households, 1980 (Box 27)
    - Background information (Box 27)
    - Presentation originals--acetates, 1989 (Box 27)
    - Standard capability presentation, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Digital
    - Briefing agenda, 1993 Sep. 29 (Box 27)
    - Company glossary, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Credentials presentation, 1993, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Digital & Its Competitors, 1993, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Digital Home & Office PC Purchase Decision-Maker Target Profiles, undated (Box 27)
    - Leverage Begins with Knowing the Consumer, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Leverage for Success, leave-behind book, 1993 Oct. 27 (Box 27)
  - Discover Card
    - Background information, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Brand personality study, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Case study, 1990 (Box 28)
    - Credit card market information, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Discover Card briefing document, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Positioning the Discover Card, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Presentation, 1987, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Project Ace, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Sear, Roebuck, & Company--Competitive Card Product Analysis, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Dole
    - JWT-USA Organization, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Presentation, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Domino's Pizza
    - Agency questions, 1990 (Box 28)
    - Credentials presentation, undated (Box 28)
  - Douglas Aircraft Company
    - General files, 1954 May-1961 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 28)
  - Drackett
    - Background information, 1990 (Box 28)
    - Credentials presentation, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Household specialty market, 1987 (Box 29)
    - S.C. Johnson/Glade, air freshener strategic overview, 1988 (Box 29)
    - Target profile, 1989 (Box 29)
  - Eastern Airlines
    - General files, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - General presentation files, 1986 (Box 29)
    - Backup scripts, undated (Box 29)
    - Bert Metter file, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
    - Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
    - Eastern facts--O'Donnell file, 1986 (Box 29)
    - Eastern Airlines versus Pan Am, script, undated (Box 29)
    - JWT company profile, 1987 (Box 30)
    - Letters to Eastern, 1987 (Box 30)
    - Marketing in the Midst of Change, 1986, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Months Ahead presentation, undated (Box 30)
    - Past presentation material, 1986 (Box 30)
    - Shuttle backup scripts, undated (Box 30)
    - Special Qualities of JWT to Serve Eastern Airlines, circa 1985 (Box 30)
    - Three Phases presentation, undated (Box 30)
  - Eckerd Drugs
    - Background Information, 1985, 2 volumes (Box 30)
  - Electrolux
    - General files, 1989 and undated (Box 30)
  - Elizabeth Arden
    - Competitive tear sheets, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Overview, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Emery
    - Credentials presentation, 1988, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Consolidated Emery preliminary media input, 1989 (Box 31)
    - International media and marketing for selected Emery markets, 1980 (Box 31)
    - Notes, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Overall advertising plan, undated (Box 31)
    - Presentation agenda, 1981 Aug. 27 (Box 31)
    - Purolator file, 1988 (Box 31)
    - Recommendations, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Eyelab
    - General files, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
    - Advertising agency register, 1988-1989 (Box 31)
    - Backup quotes, undated (Box 31)
    - Clippings, 1988-1989, 1 of 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Clippings, 1988-1989 (continued), 2 of 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Company overview, 1989, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Compensation proposal, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Competitive media spending, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Credentials presentation, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Eye care market overview, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Eyelab Does Not Have the Biggest Budget, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Making Eyelab $ Go Further, presentation, undated (Box 32)
    - Market for Ophthalmic Goods in U.S.,--competitive and business trend analyses, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Next Step presentation, 1989, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Ophthalmic practice rules, 1986 (Box 32)
    - Ophthalmic retailing market briefing, 1989 (Box 32)
    - Optical Retailing: The Plot Thickens, 1988 (Box 32)
    - Questionnaire response, 1988 (Box 33)
    - State of ophthalmic industry, 1988 (Box 33)
    - Which Way presentation, 1987 (Box 33)
  - Ferry-Morse Seed Company
    - General files, 1964 May (Box 33)
  - Fidelity
    - Unleashing the Power of the Brand, 1994, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Firestone Tire & Rubber Company
    - General files, 1961 Oct.-1961 Nov. (Bill Torrey files) (Box 33)
    - General files, 1966 May-1996 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 33)
  - First Nationwide Bank
    - General files, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Clippings, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Credentials presentation, undated (Box 33)
    - JWT-USA presentation, undated (Box 33)
    - Strategic review, 1989 (Box 33)
  - First National Bank of Miami
    - General files, 1954 Apr.-1958 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 33)
  - Fisher-Price
    - Advertising to Children, circa 1992 (Box 33)
  - Florida Department of Citrus
    - 1982 Grapefruit strategy study, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Credentials presentation, circa 1982 (Box 33)
    - JWT presentations, 1983, undated (Box 33)
    - JWT presentation book, general, undated (Box 33)
    - JWT presentation book, Fulfill the Potential, 1982 (Box 34)
    - Orange & Grapefruit Product Consumer Profile Report for 1981-1982, 1983 (Box 34)
    - Preliminary briefing, Florida grapefruit, 1982 (Box 34)
    - Preliminary data for Florida Citrus Commission, 1982 (Box 34)
    - Taste evaluation of grapefruit juice at Florida Tourists Welcome Centers, 1983 (Box 34)
    - Technical manual, 1983 (Box 34)
    - Television photoboards: grapefruit and orange fruit juices, 1982 (Box 34)
  - Florida Tourism
    - Clippings, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Request for Proposal, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Travel Pages brochure, 1987 (Box 34)
  - Florists Transworld Delivery (FTD)
    - Floral marketing report, 1985, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Project Greenbrier, 1989 (Box 34)
  - FLYMO
    - Information book, 1982 (Box 34)
    - Meeting, 1982 (Box 34)
  - Ford Motor Company
    - General files, 1954 Nov.-1964 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 34)
    - Contemporary markets program proposal, 1982 (Box 34)
    - [JWT-Australia. Ford Motor Company leave-behind books. Our Views and Strategies, Our Credentials, Why J. Walter Thompson.: Moved to Oversize Materials], 3 books (Box 34)
    - Multinational presentation, undated (Box 35)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 35)
    - Quality is Job #1 1982 Mar. 12 (Box 35)
    - World According to Weith presentation, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Worldwide offices presentation, 1978 (Box 35)
    - Worldwide organization structure, undated (Box 35)
  - Freddie Mac
    - Briefing, 1989 (Box 35)
    - Reference materials, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Frito-Lay
    - General files, 1987-1989 (Box 35)
    - Background information, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Buy study, 1980 (Box 35)
    - Clippings, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Crisis in branding, undated (Box 35)
    - Effect of media on recall testing, 1979 (Box 35)
    - Frito-Lay specifics, undated (Box 35)
    - Generic products study, implications for brand marketing and advertising, 1978 (Box 35)
    - JWT presentation, 1989 (Box 35)
    - Marketing research, 1987-1989 (Box 35)
    - Meeting agenda, 1981 Aug. 28 (Box 35)
    - Overviews, 1987-1988 (Box 35)
    - Planter's Peanuts file, competitive, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Presentation book, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Gambler Promotions
    - General files, 1972-1974 (Box 36)
  - Garrett Corporation
    - General files, 1961 Oct.-1962 (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 36)
  - Gas Association
    - General files, 1968 Sep. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 36)
  - Gerber
    - Advertising review, 1990 (Box 36)
  - Gillette
    - General files, 1959 Feb.-1966 June (Bill Torrey files) (Box 36)
    - General files, 1965 Nov.-1969 May (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 36)
  - Glidden
    - Building Blocks to a Beautiful Finish, 1994 (Box 36)
    - Glidden-JWT Master Palette, 1994 Oct. 6 (Box 36)
    - Presentation file, 1994 Oct. 6 (Box 36)
    - Supplemental analysis, 1994 (Box 36)
  - Good Humor
    - General files, 1963 Dec.-1965 Jan. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 36)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company
    - General files, 1958 May-1962 Nov. (Box 36)
    - 100 day plan, 1982 (Box 36)
    - Advertising recommendations for 2nd half, 1982 (Box 37)
    - Advertising recommendations to Goodyear Canada, 1982 (Box 37)
    - Annual report, 1988 (Box 37)
    - Campaign research, 1988-1989 (Box 37)
    - Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 37)
    - Credentials presentation, 1981 July 27 (Box 37)
    - Enthusiast's guide, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Goodyear Canada, Incorporated, including recommendations, 1981-1983 (Box 37)
    - Invoices, 1989 (Box 37)
    - JWT advertising strategy, recommendations to Goodyear, 1982 (Box 37)
    - JWT presentation, undated (Box 37)
    - [JWT-USA--Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company storyboards, undated: Moved to Oversize Materials], 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Presentation boards, 1981 (Box 37)
    - Progress report, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Review, 1981 (Box 37)
    - Scripts, 1982-1989 (Box 37)
    - Storyboards and proofs, 1990 (Box 37)
  - Grand Union
    - General files, 1981 and undated (Box 38)
    - Building a Brand presentation, undated (Box 38)
    - Credentials presentation, 1982 Jan. 5 (Box 38)
    - Outline materials, 1981-1982 (Box 38)
    - Presentation, 1982 Jan. 15, 4 folders (Box 38)
  - Häagen-Dazs
    - Category research, 1981-1983 (Box 38)
    - Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 38)
    - Consumer interviews, 1984, 1-3 of 4 folders (Box 38)
    - Consumer interviews, 1984 (continued), 4 of 4 folders (Box 39)
    - Consumer transcripts, undated (Box 39)
    - Exploration of Häagen-Dazs Brand Character, 1983 (Box 39)
    - Ice Cream Market: Business Information Report, 1984 (Box 39)
    - Maintaining the Lead presentation, undated (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous information & research, 1983-1984 (Box 39)
    - Presentation, 1984 Aug. 9 (Box 39)
    - Preserving the Magic, presentation, 1984 (Box 39)
  - Hallmark
    - General files, 1961 Mar.-1961 Dec. (Box 39)
    - Consumer interviews, 1986 (Box 39)
  - Handy Andy's
    - Winning in the Marketplace presentation, undated (Box 39)
  - Hardee's
    - Credential presentation, 1990 (Box 39)
    - Source materials for pitch, circa 1990, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Harlequin Enterprises Ltd.
    - General files, 1980-1982 (Box 40)
    - Annual reports, 1980 (Box 40)
    - Clippings, 1978 (Box 40)
    - JWT background, 1981 (Box 40)
    - Radio-TV reports, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
  - Harrah's Atlantic City
    - General files, 1984 (Box 40)
  - Harris-Lanier
    - General files, 1986 (Box 40)
  - Hart, Schaffner, & Marx
    - General files, 1971 (Box 40)
  - Hefty Bags
    - General files, 1982 (Box 40)
  - Helene Curtis Industries
    - General files, 1959 Sep.-1963 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 40)
  - Hershey Foods Corporation
    - Meeting, 1987 Nov. 8 (Box 40)
  - Hertz
    - General files, 1981-1984 (Box 40)
    - Credentials presentation, 1981 (Box 40)
    - Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 40)
    - Ryder versus Hertz-Penske, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Hiram Walker
    - Branding Vodka, 1993 (Box 40)
  - H.J. Heinz
    - General files, 1987 and 1989, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Condiments situation analysis, 1987 (Box 41)
  - Home Box Office (HBO)
    - General files, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Agency orientation, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Alphabetical market index of local systems, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Between Friends script, undated (Box 41)
    - Clippings, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Competitive copy samples, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Creative direction, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Credentials presentation, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Donaldson, Lufkin & Jenrette industry viewpoint, 1982 (Box 41)
    - Door-to-door sales Co-op campaign, 1983 (Box 41)
    - HBO: The First 10 Years, 1982 (Box 41)
    - JWT Cable Capsules, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Lansdowne: competitive pay-TV media expenditures, 1981-1982 (Box 41)
    - Presentation & research, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Proofs, 1984 (Box 41)
    - Schweitzer (Peter) notes, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Segmentation research on the cable/pay market, 1983 (Box 41)
    - Segmentation study of the urban/suburban cable television market, 1983 (Box 42)
    - Summary of agency brief, 1983, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Hola (news magazine, Spain)
    - Meeting minutes, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Household Finance Corporation (HFC)
    - General files, 1982-1983 (Box 42)
  - Hyatt Hotels Corporation
    - General files, 1978 (Box 42)
    - Agency questionnaire, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Competitive Hotel Advertising, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Credentials presentation, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Effectiveness presentation, 1993 (Box 42)
    - Hill Holiday & JWT Historical, 1992 (Box 42)
    - How Can JWT Help Hyatt Achieve Growth in the 1990's, 1993 Jan. 25, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Questionnaire-correspondence, JWT history, 1992 (Box 43)
    - U.S. Hotel & Resort Industry: Fact Book 1991 (Box 43)
    - What Happens When I Get There? Hilton International presentation, 1992 (Box 43)
    - Worldwide guide, 1992-1993 (Box 43)
  - Iceland Tourism
    - General files, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
  - Institute of Life Insurance
    - General files, 1956 June-1957 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 43)
  - Insurance Institute for Highway Safety
    - General files, 1961 May-Sep. (Bill Torrey files) (Box 43)
  - Interface Flooring
    - General files, 1983 (Box 43)
  - International Business Machines (IBM)
    - Annual report, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Consumer interviews, Chicago, 1986 June 18 (Box 43)
    - Consumer interviews, Los Angeles, 1986 June 20 (Box 43)
    - Consumer interviews, New York City, 1986 June 19 (Box 43)
    - Credentials presentation, 1986, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - General systems division presentation, 1980 (Box 44)
    - Marketing image copy presentation, 1987 (Box 44)
    - New business presentation, 1979 (Box 44)
    - Overview of corporate campaigns, undated (Box 44)
    - Presentation background, 1986 (Box 44)
    - Printer file, 1979-1986, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Senior management interviews, 1986-1987, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Thumbnail competitive creative review, 1986 (Box 44)
  - International Consulting Enterprises (ICE)
    - General files, 1987 (Box 44)
  - International Correspondence Schools (ICS)
    - General files, 1984 (Box 44)
  - International Gold Corporation
    - General files, 1987 (Box 44)
    - Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 44)
    - Promotional literature, 1986-1987 (Box 44)
    - Tear sheets, 1986-1987 (Box 44)
  - Intercontinental Hotels Corporation
    - General files, 1957 Nov. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 44)
  - Investment Company Institute
    - Advertising Media Alternatives, 1987 (Box 45)
    - Annual report, 1986 (Box 45)
    - Selecting & Managing an Advertising Agency, 1987 (Box 45)
    - Seminar, 1987 (Box 45)
  - Irish Tourist Board
    - General files, 1987 (Box 45)
  - Irving Trust Company
    - General files, 1953 Aug.-1962 Aug. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 45)
  - ISACOMM
    - Presentations, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Italian Swiss Colony (wines)
    - Presentation, 1983 (Box 45)
  - IZOD
    - Briefing, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Consumer interview transcripts, 1984 (Box 45)
    - General Mills Fashion Group file, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 45)
    - Store checks, 1984 (Box 45)
  - Jamaica Tourist Board
    - General files, 1981 (Box 45)
  - Jaylis
    - General files, 1961 May-1962 Sep. (Box 46)
  - Jenny Craig
    - Presentation, 1989 July 18 (Box 46)
  - Johnson & Johnson
    - General files, 1980-1985, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Advertising & marketing intelligence reports, 1980-1981 (Box 46)
    - Brand utility yardstick, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Branded products at the crossroads, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Category loyalty rankings, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Clippings, 1975-1981 (Box 46)
    - Cold-flu file, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Feminine care products presentation, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Feminine hygiene background file, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Meeting agenda, 1985 Aug. 12 (Box 46)
    - Bert Metter Johnson & Johnson reel, 1985 (Box 47)
    - New business workbook, 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - O.B. tampons campaign, 1982 (Box 47)
    - Overview, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Presentations, 1984-1985 and undated, 4 folders (Box 47)
    - Television copy evaluation, undated (Box 47)
  - Johnson Motors
    - General files, 1955 Dec. (Box 47)
  - Jos. A. Schlitz
    - Capabilities review, 1981 Sep. 29 (Box 47)
  - JVC
    - General files, 1983 (Box 47)
  - Kaiser/Health America
    - General files, 1984 (Box 47)
  - Kellogg's
    - All Bran case history, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Presentation, 1977 (Box 48)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken (KFC)
    - General files, 1987 (Box 48)
    - Focus group summary, 1986 (Box 48)
    - Home delivery situation audit, 1988 (Box 48)
    - JWT opportunities, undated (Box 48)
    - Questionnaire responses, 1987 (Box 48)
    - Pizza Category and Pizza Hut, 1987 (Box 48)
    - Presentation agenda, undated (Box 48)
    - Research and background, 1988 (Box 48)
  - Kinney Shoes
    - General files, 1987-1988 (Box 48)
  - K-Mart
    - Brief, 1987 (Box 48)
    - Credentials and credibility preview, 1987 (Box 48)
    - Information for Mr. Alvin A. Achenbaum, Achenbaum Associates, Incorporated, 1995 (Box 48)
  - KNBC-TV
    - General files, 1964 Aug. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 48)
  - Kodak
    - General files, 1954 Apr.-1965 Apr. (Box 48)
    - Account plan, 1982 (Box 48)
    - Advertising budget, recommendation, and 1983 media plan, 1982 (Box 48)
    - Attitudes of Amateur and Professional Photographers Toward 35 Millimeter Color Print Films, 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Copy Research Evaluation of Introductory and Satisfactory Disc Camera Advertising, 1982 (Box 49)
    - Delta-Atlanta transcripts, 1984 (Box 49)
    - Delta-Chicago transcripts, 1984, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Delta-New York transcripts, 1984 (Box 49)
    - Ektaprint copier target plan, 1975 (Box 49)
    - Film management review, 1986 (Box 49)
    - Kodak batteries business review, 1988 Sep. (Box 49)
    - Kodak Reinvents Film presentation, undated (Box 49)
    - Presentation, 1977 (Box 49a)
    - Presentation transparencies, 1982 (Box 49a)
    - Proofs, 1979-1982 (Box 50)
    - P-189 model files, 1981-1982 (Box 50)
      [New line of 35mm color film.]
    - Situation analysis, 1982 (Box 50)
    - Strategic Opportunities: The Future, 1982 (Box 50)
    - Taking on the Establishment presentation, undated (Box 50)
    - What Works for Kodak Advertising, 1982 (Box 50)
  - Koor Industries
    - General files, 1985 (Box 50)
  - Kraft Foods Company
    - General files, 1954 Feb.-1962 May (Box 50)
    - Brand Realities: Implications for Coffee Brands in Europe, 1993 (Box 50)
    - Case histories, 1982-1986 (Box 50)
    - Cheese project, 1984 (Box 50)
    - Competitive file, undated (Box 50)
    - Cottage cheese interview transcripts, 1988 (Box 50)
    - Cottage cheese positioning, undated (Box 50)
    - Cottage cheese synectics session, 1988 (Box 50)
    - Dairy group presentation book, 1988 (Box 50)
    - Dairy products, 1986-1988 (Box 51)
    - Effectiveness presentation leave-behind book, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Igniting Brand Equity presentation (never used) 1993 June (Box 51)
    - JWT presentation, 1988 (Box 51)
    - [JWT-USA-- Kraft--NatuBlend spreads, undated: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 51)
    - Kraft-General Foods merger analysis, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Leave-behind book, 1988 (Box 51)
    - Nutrition issues file, 1988-1990 (Box 51)
    - Presentation, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Presentation to Tom Herskovits, 1988 (Box 51)
    - Project Simple: Process Versus Ingredient, 1988 (Box 51)
    - Sliced natural cheese pre-test, 1979 (Box 51)
    - Slides not used, 1988 (Box 51)
    - Trailblazer, Bert Metter review, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Trailblazer communications strategy recommendation, 1989 (Box 52)
    - Umbrella cheese project, 1989 (Box 52)
    - What is Cottage Cheese to You? presentation, undated (Box 52)
  - Kuppenheimer
    - General files, 1983-1985 (Box 52)
    - Presentation file, 1984 (Box 52)
    - T-plan, 1985 (Box 52)
  - Lawrence Radiation Laboratory
    - General files, 1956 June-1959 Oct. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 52)
  - Lee Jeans
    - Building for Tomorrow--A Discussion Starter, 1993 (Box 52)
  - Leeming-Pacquin
    - General files, 1981-1982 (Box 52)
    - Cable capsules, 1982 (Box 52)
    - JWT profile, 1982 (Box 52)
    - Presentation outline, 1982 (Box 52)
  - Libby, McNeill & Libby
    - General files, 1954-Dec.-1964 Sep. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 52)
  - Liebig (OXO) International
    - General files, 1961 Jan.-1961 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 52)
  - Liggett & Myers Tobacco Company
    - General files, 1958 Jan.-1964 Nov. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 52)
  - Lipton
    - General files, 1987 (Box 52)
    - Consumer interviews, 1986-1987, 5 folders (Box 53)
    - Introducing Herb-Ox presentation (R.T. French), 1986 (Box 53)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 53)
  - Little Caesar Enterprises
    - General files, 1992 and undated (Box 53)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 53)
  - L.L. Bean
    - Catalog arena presentation, 1985 (Box 53)
    - [Connecting People Outdoors Since 1912, 2005: Moved to Restricted Materials] (Box 53)
    - Consumer interviews--Hartford, 1986 (Box 53)
    - Consumer interviews--Los Angeles--releases and topsheets, 1986 (Box 53)
    - Consumer interviews--New York, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Presentation file, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Presentation of agency capabilities, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Presentations, 1986 and undated, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Loctite
    - Background, 1981 (Box 54)
    - JWT profile, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Preliminary situational analysis, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Presentation, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Recommendations for long-term strategic marketing, 1983 (Box 54)
  - L.O.F. Glass
    - General files, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Löwenbräu
    - Brand review, 1985 (Box 54)
    - Clippings, 1977-1985 (Box 54)
    - [JWT-USA--Löwenbräu market research, 1985: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 54)
    - Lion's Share presentation, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Market research, 1984-1985 (Box 55)
    - Positioning, 1985 (Box 55)
  - M. Lowenstein Corporation
    - General files, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Lowrey Organ Company
    - General files, 1958 Aug.-1958 Sep. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 55)
  - Magnavox
    - Clippings, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Maidenform
    - Leave-behind book, 1986 (Box 55)
    - Presentations, 1986-1991, 4 folders (Box 55)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust
    - General files, 1984-1987 (Box 55)
    - Background information presentation, 1982-1985 (Box 55)